<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Preview Video</string>

    <!-- EntryPoint -->
    <string name="toast_appNotFound">The package \'%s\' can\'t be opened.</string>
    <string name="toast_noApps">No apps available</string>
    <string name="toast_noChooser">Can\'t open chooser</string>
    <string name="title_chooser">Choose app</string>

    <!-- MainActivity -->
    <string name="a_about">About</string>
    <string name="txt_about">"With this app you can open YouTube videos as an immobile popup on the middle of the screen that is closed automatically when the video ends, or can be closed with a single click on the back button.

App created by TrianguloY.

Notice: This app is not affiliated with YouTube nor Google. This is a third party app that uses the YouTube Api and doesn't replace any of the YouTube features."</string>
    <string name="toast_noBrowser">Can\'t open the browser</string>
    <string name="btn_appPage">Open app page</string>
    <string name="btn_openStore">Open Play store</string>
    <string name="abt_shareStore">Share app</string>

    <string name="a_setup">Setup</string>
    <string name="txt_setAsDefault">"This app is currently not shown when opening Youtube Links. To be able to select this app you must allow it by following this instructions:
1) Press the button to open the Android Settings.
2) Go to 'Open by default' (you may need to press on 'Advanced' first)
3) Select 'Open supported links'->'Open in this app' (even though it is called that, you will be asked which app you prefer to set as the default)"</string>
    <string name="btn_setAsDefault">Android settings</string>
    <string name="toast_noSettings">Can\'t open the Android settings</string>
    <string name="desc_app">Choose what app to open. Note: even if this app is set as the default, it will show a dialog to choose between opening as preview or not.</string>
    <string name="spinner_none">None</string>
    <string name="desc_fullscreen">Display videos in landscape fullscreen instead.</string>
    <string name="chx_fullscreen">Landscape fullscreen</string>
    <string name="txt_testLink">Example video: Click the link to test the app (the video is just the default Youtube logo).</string>
    <string name="txtL_testLink">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y7dpJ0oseIA</string>
    <string name="txt_opener">The current Android setting is set to open YouTube links with the app: \'%s\'. You can press the button to open that app\'s Settings and try to change it.</string>

    <!-- General -->
    <string name="toast_error">An error occurred</string>

</resources>
